Murder isn't always a crime.
Double Jeopardy is a drama, thriller, mystery film directed by Bruce Beresford.
Libby Parsons, wrongly convicted for her husband Nick's murder, thinks he is
still alive and wants to settle the score and find their son.
As she has been tried for the crime, she cannot be
re-prosecuted if she finds and kills Nick.
Libby Parsons, played by Ashley Judd.
Travis Lehman, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Nick Parsons, played by Bruce Greenwood.
Angie Green, played by Annabeth Gish.
Matty Parsons, Age 4, played by Benjamin Weir.
Bobby Long, played by Jay Brazeau.
Double Jeopardy is a 1999 American crime thriller film directed by Bruce
Beresford, and starring Ashley Judd, Tommy Lee Jones, and Bruce Greenwood.
The overall narrative is very similar to that of The
Fugitive, in which Tommy Lee Jones also plays.
Released on September 24, 1999, the film received mixed
reviews from critics and grossed $177 million.
The film explores themes of sailboat, court case, sailing
trip, new orleans, louisiana, ferry boat.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.